Guide to the Time Inc. Time Editorial Records 1938-2009 MS 3009-RG 7
New-York Historical Society
- Series III.A. Art Department: Cover Researcher Rosemary Frank Files, 1948-2009 (bulk 1963-1988); 20 Linear feet in 20 record cartons
  According to an FYI article published upon her retirement in 1984, Rosemary Frank had been with Time for 37 years. She first appears on the masthead in January 1947 as an Editorial Researcher. The October 18, 1968 Time Publisher's Letter states Frank had been a Covers Researcher for four years although she shows up in the records working on covers around 1961. By October 1970, she is listed on the Time masthead in Covers as part of the Art Department. By the 1980s, Frank is also considered the curator of the Time art collection.
  Frank arranged travel for artists, tracked their expenses, collected photographs for artists to work from or arranged sittings, scouted galleries for new talent, and screened all unsolicited artwork submitted to Time. She also served as a contact for the gift of Time Inc.'s cover art collection to the National Portrait Gallery.
  Rosemary Frank's files include her administrative files on the overall Time cover collection and her Time cover artist files. As a quirk of her job, Frank sometimes uses Time cover templates to write memoranda or take notes.
  Organized into two subseries:
  Subseries III.A.1. Administrative Files
  Subseries III.A.2. Artist Files
  - Subseries III.A.1. Administrative Files, 1974-1984; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Rosemary Frank's administrative files document her inventory by location of the Time cover art, covers and art loaned out for exhibition, and coordination of the donation and transfer to the National Portrait Gallery of the Smithsonian Institution.
    - Contract Forms / Rights and Reproduction, 1975-1982 (Offsite-box 2589, Folder 1a)
    - Inventory, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 2589, Folder 1b-18)
    - Loans: General, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 2589, Folder 19-22)
    - Loans: United States Information Agency (USIA), 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 2590, Folder 1-7)
      Folder 5 includes audiovisual material.
      1 audiocassette (MC-60BM): analog; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "ABC Review Time Exhibit."
    - National Portrait Gallery Gift, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 2590, Folder 8-13)
    - National Portrait Gallery Gift [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
  - Subseries III.A.2. Artist Files, 1948-2009 (bulk 1963-1988); 18 Linear feet in 18 record cartons
    Artists Files include records kept on artists either hired to create a Time cover or research on artists that interested Frank. Materials include examples of art in the form of prints, exhibition catalogues, slides, and photographs; correspondence; receipts of payment; news clippings; and notes including artist contact information. Files are primarily labeled with the artist's name though a few are titled with an institution or topic. Topics include cover theme, medium, nationality, style, or culture. Later records are correspondence from the Time Inc. Archives responding to requests about these files.
    - Abbett, Bob (Offsite-box 851, Folder 1)
    - Abeles, Sigmund (Offsite-box 851, Folder 2)
    - Acosta, Manuel Gregorio (Offsite-box 851, Folder 3)
    - Adams, Eddie (Offsite-box 851, Folder 4)
    - Adams, Norman (Offsite-box 851, Folder 5)
    - Adelman, Seymour (Offsite-box 851, Folder 6)
    - African American Artists and Photographers, 1964-1974 (Offsite-box 851, Folder 7a)
    - Ajin, Wizard (Offsite-box 851, Folder 7b)
    - Albertson, Lee (Offsite-box 851, Folder 8)
    - Alcorn, Bob (Offsite-box 851, Folder 9)
    - Alcorn, John (Offsite-box 851, Folder 10)
    - Aldridge, Alan (Offsite-box 851, Folder 11)
    - Allen, Julian (Offsite-box 851, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Thomas B. (Offsite-box 851, Folder 13)
    - Ameijide, Roy (Offsite-box 851, Folder 14)
    - Amsel, Richard (Offsite-box 851, Folder 15-16)
    - Anderson, Roy (Offsite-box 851, Folder 17)
    - Anderson, Dick (Offsite-box 851, Folder 18)
    - Andrea, Jerry (Offsite-box 851, Folder 19)
    - Annigoni, Pietro (Offsite-box 851, Folder 20-21)
    - Ansado, John (Offsite-box 851, Folder 22)
    - Anthony, Carol (Offsite-box 851, Folder 23)
    - Anton, Valkev (Offsite-box 851, Folder 24)
    - Appel, Karel (Offsite-box 851, Folder 25)
    - Argenziano, Joe (Offsite-box 851, Folder 26)
    - Arikha, Avigdor (Offsite-box 851, Folder 27)
    - Arisman, Marshall (Offsite-box 851, Folder 28)
    - Arnoldi, Per (Offsite-box 851, Folder 29)
    - Artzybasheff, Boris (Offsite-box 851, Folder 30-33)
    - Artzybasheff, Boris [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Ascherl, Joseph (Offsite-box 851, Folder 34)
    - Asian Whiz Kids (Offsite-box 851, Folder 35)
    - Atterby, Charles (Offsite-box 851, Folder 36)
    - Attic, David (Offsite-box 851, Folder 37)
    - Avedon, Richard (Offsite-box 851, Folder 38)
    - Bachardy, Don (Offsite-box 851, Folder 39)
    - Backer, Lutz (Offsite-box 851, Folder 40)
    - Bacon, Francis (Offsite-box 851, Folder 41)
    - Bahrs, Gajus (Offsite-box 851, Folder 42)
    - Bailey, Jack Leland (Offsite-box 851, Folder 43)
    - Bailey, William (Offsite-box 851, Folder 44)
    - Baker, Ernest Hamlin (Offsite-box 851, Folder 45)
    - Baker, Robert (Offsite-box 851, Folder 46)
    - Baldanski, Karen (Offsite-box 851, Folder 47)
    - Bama, James (Offsite-box 851, Folder 48)
    - Barkley, James (Offsite-box 851, Folder 49)
    - Barnes, Roger (Offsite-box 851, Folder 50)
    - Barnet, Will (Offsite-box 851, Folder 51)
    - Barr, Diane (Offsite-box 851, Folder 52)
    - Barracca, Sal (Offsite-box 851, Folder 53)
    - Barsotti, Charles (Offsite-box 851, Folder 54)
    - Bascove, Barbara (Offsite-box 851, Folder 55)
    - Baskin, Leonard (Offsite-box 851, Folder 56)
    - Basso, Bill (Offsite-box 851, Folder 57)
    - Battagla, Aureluis (Offsite-box 851, Folder 58)
    - Bearden, Rowan (Offsite-box 851, Folder 59)
    - Baz, Ben-Hur (Offsite-box 851, Folder 60)
    - Beal, Jack (Offsite-box 851, Folder 61)
    - Beckman, William (Offsite-box 851, Folder 62)
    - Belkin, Arnold (Offsite-box 851, Folder 63)
    - Benton, Thomas Hart (Offsite-box 851, Folder 64)
    - Berks, Robert (Offsite-box 851, Folder 65-66)
    - Berman, Sam (Offsite-box 851, Folder 67)
    - Berran, Bob (Offsite-box 851, Folder 68)
    - Besser, Arne (Offsite-box 851, Folder 69)
    - Binzen, Bill (Offsite-box 851, Folder 70)
    - Bishop, Isabel (Offsite-box 851, Folder 71)
    - Blackwell, Garie (Offsite-box 852, Folder 1)
    - Blagden, Allen (Offsite-box 852, Folder 2)
    - Blechman, R.O. (Offsite-box 852, Folder 3)
    - Blegvad, Erik (Offsite-box 852, Folder 4)
    - Block, Herbert (Offsite-box 852, Folder 5)
    - BMA Associates, Inc. (Offsite-box 852, Folder 6)
    - Bogat, Regina (Offsite-box 852, Folder 7)
    - Boghosian, Varnjan (Offsite-box 852, Folder 8)
    - Bohrod, Aaron (Offsite-box 852, Folder 9)
    - Bomar, Walter (Offsite-box 852, Folder 10)
    - Bomberger, Bruce (Offsite-box 852, Folder 11)
    - Boobis, Bradford (Offsite-box 852, Folder 12)
    - Bordelon, Melinda (Offsite-box 852, Folder 13)
    - Borne, Mortimer (Offsite-box 852, Folder 14)
    - Bornstein, Marguerita (Offsite-box 852, Folder 15)
    - Borst, Herb (Offsite-box 852, Folder 16)
    - Bosc, Ron (Offsite-box 852, Folder 17)
    - Bouche, Rene (Offsite-box 852, Folder 18)
    - Bouldin, Marshall (Offsite-box 852, Folder 19)
    - Bowler, Joe (Offsite-box 852, Folder 20)
    - Boyle, Neil (Offsite-box 851, Folder 21)
    - Brack, Dennis (Offsite-box 852, Folder 22)
    - Bradac, Jaroslav (Offsite-box 852, Folder 23)
    - Bragg, Charles (Offsite-box 852, Folder 24)
    - Brainard, Joe (Offsite-box 852, Folder 25)
    - Bralow, Gary (Offsite-box 852, Folder 26)
    - Bravo, Claudio (Offsite-box 852, Folder 27)
    - Brennan, Hank (Offsite-box 852, Folder 28)
    - Breslow, J.H. (Offsite-box 852, Folder 29)
    - Breswitz, Ralph (Offsite-box 852, Folder 30)
    - Breverman, Harvey (Offsite-box 852, Folder 31)
    - Brickner, Alice (Offsite-box 852, Folder 32)
    - British, French, Italian Portraitists (Offsite-box 852, Folder 33)
    - Brofsky, Miriam (Offsite-box 852, Folder 34)
    - Brown, D.P. (Offsite-box 852, Folder 35)
    - Browning, Colleen (Offsite-box 852, Folder 36)
    - Bruner, Paul (Offsite-box 852, Folder 37)
    - Bueb, Franz (Offsite-box 852, Folder 38)
    - Buerge, Bill (Offsite-box 852, Folder 39)
    - Buffet, Bernard (Offsite-box 852, Folder 40)
    - Burket, Nancy Ekholm (Offsite-box 852, Folder 41)
    - Burrell, Fred (Offsite-box 852, Folder 42)
    - Burroughs, Miggs (Offsite-box 852, Folder 43)
    - Bury, Pol (Offsite-box 852, Folder 44)
    - Butler, Patricia (Offsite-box 852, Folder 45)
    - Byrd, David Edward (Offsite-box 852, Folder 46)
    - Calabrese, Vincent (Offsite-box 852, Folder 47)
    - Callahan, Kevin (Offsite-box 852, Folder 48)
    - Calle, Paul (Offsite-box 852, Folder 49)
    - Camilleri, Stephanie (Offsite-box 852, Folder 50)
    - Camin, Mal (Offsite-box 852, Folder 51)
    - Campbell, Frederick (Offsite-box 852, Folder 52)
    - Campbell, Jim (Offsite-box 852, Folder 53)
    - Canadian Artists (Offsite-box 852, Folder 54)
    - Caniff, Milton (Offsite-box 852, Folder 55)
    - Candela, Janice (Offsite-box 852, Folder 56)
    - Canton, Shelley (Offsite-box 852, Folder 57)
    - Caras, Peter (Offsite-box 852, Folder 58)
    - Carey, Martin (Offsite-box 852, Folder 59)
    - Carnet for Matthew Klein (Offsite-box 853, Folder 1)
    - Carney, Harald E. (Offsite-box 853, Folder 2)
    - Carrera, Maria (Offsite-box 853, Folder 3)
    - Caval, Bill (Offsite-box 853, Folder 4)
    - Carroll, Walter (Offsite-box 853, Folder 5)
    - Carruthers, Roy (Offsite-box 853, Folder 6)
    - Cayard, Bruce (Offsite-box 853, Folder 7)
    - Chagnoux, Christine (Offsite-box 853, Folder 8)
    - Chapin, James (Offsite-box 853, Folder 9)
    - Charlot, Jean (Offsite-box 853, Folder 10)
    - Charmatz, Bill (Offsite-box 853, Folder 11)
    - Cheetham, Jack and Betty (Offsite-box 853, Folder 12)
    - Chermayeff & Geismar Associates Inc. (Offsite-box 853, Folder 13)
    - Chryssa (Offsite-box 853, Folder 14)
    - Chwast, Seymour (Offsite-box 853, Folder 15)
    - Ciccone, Antonio (Offsite-box 853, Folder 16)
    - Clark, Tom (Offsite-box 853, Folder 17)
    - Cleeland, David (Offsite-box 853, Folder 18)
    - Clift, John (Offsite-box 853, Folder 19)
    - Clifton, Michelle Gamm (Offsite-box 853, Folder 20)
    - Cline, John Douglas (Offsite-box 853, Folder 21)
    - Close, Chuck (Offsite-box 853, Folder 22)
    - Cloud Studios (Offsite-box 853, Folder 23)
    - Cober, Alan E. (Offsite-box 853, Folder 24)
    - Coconis, Ted (Offsite-box 853, Folder 25)
    - Collagists (Offsite-box 853, Folder 26)
    - Collier, Pat (Offsite-box 853, Folder 27)
    - Colos, Francois (Offsite-box 853, Folder 28)
    - Connelly, Brian (Offsite-box 853, Folder 29)
    - Conover, Marilyn (Offsite-box 853, Folder 30)
    - Conrad, Paul (Offsite-box 853, Folder 31)
    - Constitution (Offsite-box 853, Folder 32)
    - Constitution [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Conway, Fred (Offsite-box 853, Folder 33)
    - Cooper, Heather (Offsite-box 853, Folder 34)
    - Cooper, James (Offsite-box 853, Folder 35)
    - Corey, Chris (Offsite-box 853, Folder 36)
    - Cornell, Thomas (Offsite-box 853, Folder 37)
    - Cowan, Frank (Offsite-box 853, Folder 38)
    - Cox, Gardner (Offsite-box 853, Folder 39)
    - Craft, Kinuko (Offsite-box 853, Folder 40)
    - Crandall, Robert S. (Offsite-box 853, Folder 41)
    - Crate (for storage) (Offsite-box 853, Folder 42)
    - Cristiano, Rudy (Offsite-box 853, Folder 43)
    - Csakany, Gabriel (Offsite-box 853, Folder 44)
    - Csatari, Joe (Offsite-box 853, Folder 45)
    - Cuevas, Jose Luis (Offsite-box 853, Folder 46)
    - Cummings, Willard W. (Offsite-box 853, Folder 47)
    - Curlee, Lynn (Offsite-box 853, Folder 48)
    - Curie, Gordon (Offsite-box 853, Folder 49)
    - Cusack, Margaret (Offsite-box 853, Folder 50)
    - Cushner, Bill (Offsite-box 853, Folder 51)
    - Czermanski, Zdzislaw (Offsite-box 853, Folder 52)
    - Dall, Martin M. (Offsite-box 853, Folder 53-54)
    - Dalton, Ann (Offsite-box 853, Folder 55)
    - Danby, Ken (Offsite-box 853, Folder 56)
    - D'Andrea, Bernard (Offsite-box 853, Folder 57)
    - D'Arcangelo, Alan [Allen?] (Offsite-box 853, Folder 58)
    - Darcy, Tom (Offsite-box 853, Folder 59)
    - Davidson, Everett (Offsite-box 853, Folder 60)
    - Davidson, Herb (Offsite-box 853, Folder 61)
    - Davidson, Jo (Offsite-box 853, Folder 62)
    - Davis, Jack (Offsite-box 853, Folder 63)
    - Davis, Paul (Offsite-box 854, Folder 1-2)
    - Davis, Lawrence Cade (Offsite-box 854, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Vestie (Offsite-box 854, Folder 4)
    - Davison, Philip Charles (Offsite-box 854, Folder 5)
    - Davisson, Zita (Offsite-box 854, Folder 6)
    - Degkwitz, Hermann (Offsite-box 854, Folder 7)
    - De Hory, Elmyr (Offsite-box 854, Folder 8)
    - De Kooning, Elaine (Offsite-box 854, Folder 9)
    - De Kooning, Willem (Offsite-box 854, Folder 10)
    - De Ruth, Jan (Offsite-box 854, Folder 11)
    - Delaney, Beauford (Offsite-box 854, Folder 12)
    - Delfino, Matt (Offsite-box 854, Folder 13)
    - De Lesseps, Tauni (Offsite-box 854, Folder 14)
    - Del Grosso, James (Offsite-box 854, Folder 15)
    - De Mejo, Oscar (Offsite-box 854, Folder 16)
    - Dengrove, Ada L. (Offsite-box 854, Folder 17)
    - Deniega, Edward (Offsite-box 854, Folder 18)
    - Denzinger, Katharina (Offsite-box 854, Folder 19)
    - DesCombes, Roland (Offsite-box 854, Folder 20)
    - Designers and Partners Incorporated (Offsite-box 854, Folder 21)
    - Dewey, Ken (Offsite-box 854, Folder 22)
    - Dickinson, Geoffrey (Offsite-box 854, Folder 23)
    - Dickinson, Nancy (Offsite-box 854, Folder 24)
    - Diffenderfer, Ed (Offsite-box 854, Folder 25)
    - Dill, Terry Lee (Offsite-box 854, Folder 26)
    - Dinnerstein, Harvey (Offsite-box 854, Folder 27)
    - Dobell, William (Offsite-box 854, Folder 28-29)
    - Doherty, Norman (Offsite-box 854, Folder 30)
    - Domingez, Elias (Offsite-box 854, Folder 31)
    - Donati, Lazzaro (Offsite-box 854, Folder 32)
    - Donizetti, Mario (Offsite-box 854, Folder 33)
    - Doret.Michael (Offsite-box 854, Folder 34-35)
    - Dorsey, Paul (Offsite-box 854, Folder 36)
    - Dream Photo Factory (Offsite-box 854, Folder 37)
    - Driver, Raymond (Offsite-box 854, Folder 38)
    - Drossman, Allan (Offsite-box 854, Folder 39)
    - Drucker, Mort (Offsite-box 854, Folder 40-41)
    - Dulaney, Dick (Offsite-box 854, Folder 42)
    - Duncan, Scott (Offsite-box 854, Folder 43)
    - Durchanek, Ludvik (Offsite-box 854, Folder 44)
    - Eagle, Mike (Offsite-box 854, Folder 45)
    - Edelman, Yrjö (Offsite-box 854, Folder 46)
    - Edwards, William (Offsite-box 854, Folder 47)
    - Eisner, Michael (Offsite-box 854, Folder 48)
    - Ely, Richard (Offsite-box 854, Folder 49)
    - Emett, Rowland (Offsite-box 854, Folder 50)
    - English, Mark (Offsite-box 854, Folder 51)
    - English, Michael (Offsite-box 854, Folder 52)
    - Enos, Randall (Offsite-box 854, Folder 53)
    - Erbe, Gary (Offsite-box 854, Folder 54)
    - Ervin, Wilma (Offsite-box 854, Folder 55)
    - Escher, Maurits Cornelis (Offsite-box 855, Folder 1)
    - Escobar, Marisol (Offsite-box 855, Folder 2)
    - Estes, Richard (Offsite-box 855, Folder 3)
    - Eubanks, Tony (Offsite-box 855, Folder 4)
    - Eula, Joe (Offsite-box 855, Folder 5)
    - Facci, Domenico (Offsite-box 855, Folder 6)
    - Farris, Joseph G. (Offsite-box 855, Folder 7)
    - Fasolino, Teresa (Offsite-box 855, Folder 8)
    - Feldman, R. (Offsite-box 855, Folder 9)
    - Fern, David (Offsite-box 855, Folder 10)
    - Fernandez, Julio (Offsite-box 855, Folder 11-12)
    - Ferg, Guy (Offsite-box 855, Folder 13)
    - Fillie, Robert (Offsite-box 855, Folder 14)
    - Fine, Peter (Offsite-box 855, Folder 15)
    - Finster, Howard (Offsite-box 855, Folder 16)
    - Fitch, Kelly (Offsite-box 855, Folder 17)
    - Fitzgerald, Frank (Offsite-box 855, Folder 18)
    - Fitzgerald, Ken (Offsite-box 855, Folder 19)
    - Flackman, David (Offsite-box 855, Folder 20)
    - Flamm, Roy (Offsite-box 855, Folder 21)
    - Flemming, Guy (Offsite-box 855, Folder 22)
    - Fleminger, Irwin (Offsite-box 855, Folder 23)
    - Flora, James (Offsite-box 855, Folder 24)
    - Florian, Douglas (Offsite-box 855, Folder 25)
    - Folon, Jean-Michel (Offsite-box 855, Folder 26-27)
    - Forbes, Bart (Offsite-box 855, Folder 28)
    - Foreman, Mike (Offsite-box 855, Folder 29)
    - Fotis (Offsite-box 855, Folder 30)
    - Fox, Barbara (Offsite-box 855, Folder 31)
    - Fox, Lorraine (Offsite-box 855, Folder 32)
    - Francois, Andre (Offsite-box 855, Folder 33)
    - Frascino, Edward (Offsite-box 855, Folder 34)
    - Frasconi, Antonio (Offsite-box 855, Folder 35)
    - Fredman, Denny (Offsite-box 855, Folder 36)
    - Freud, Lucian (Offsite-box 855, Folder 37)
    - Fricks, David (Offsite-box 855, Folder 38)
    - Frisch, Marianne Brunson (Offsite-box 855, Folder 39)
    - Fuchs, Bernie (Offsite-box 855, Folder 40)
    - Fryita, Neil (Offsite-box 855, Folder 41)
    - Funk, Mitchell (Offsite-box 855, Folder 42)
    - Gaetano, Nicholas (Offsite-box 855, Folder 43)
    - Gallardo, Gervasio (Offsite-box 855, Folder 44)
    - Gallo, Frank (Offsite-box 855, Folder 45)
    - Gallo, Samuel (Offsite-box 855, Folder 46)
    - Gammel, Stephen (Offsite-box 855, Folder 47)
    - Gammon, Reginald (Offsite-box 855, Folder 48)
    - Gantner, Bernard (Offsite-box 855, Folder 49)
    - Garrido, Hector (Offsite-box 855, Folder 50)
    - Gassoumis, Demetri (Offsite-box 855, Folder 51)
    - Geary, Kevin (Offsite-box 855, Folder 52)
    - Gee, Peter (Offsite-box 855, Folder 53)
    - Gelb, C.E. (Offsite-box 855, Folder 54)
    - Gerber, Larry (Offsite-box 855, Folder 55)
    - German Artists (Offsite-box 855, Folder 56)
    - Gersten, Gerry (Offsite-box 855, Folder 57)
    - Gescheidt, Alfred (Offsite-box 855, Folder 58)
    - Getz, Arthur (Offsite-box 855, Folder 59)
    - Giacometti, Alberto (Offsite-box 855, Folder 60)
    - Gigli, Ormond (Offsite-box 855, Folder 61)
    - Gilbert, John (Offsite-box 855, Folder 62-63)
    - Gill, James (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 1)
    - Gillespie, Gregory (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 2)
    - Giovanopoulos, Paul (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 3-4)
    - Giuliani, Vin (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 5)
    - Giusti, George (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 6-7)
    - Giusti, Robert (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 8)
    - Glanzman, Louis S. (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 9)
    - Glaser, Milton (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 10)
    - Glanbach, Stanley (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 11)
    - Glick, Laurie (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 12)
    - Glinsky, Vincent (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 13)
    - Gnidziejko, Alex (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 14-15)
    - Gorsline, Douglas (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 16)
    - Goslin, Charles (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 17)
    - Goslin, Charles and David Barnett (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 18)
    - Grace, Roy (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 19)
    - Goetz, Bernard (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 20)
    - Goldberg, Elias (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 21)
    - Goldwater, Barry: Cover (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 22)
    - Gonzales, Ben (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 23)
    - Gooch, Gerald (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 24)
    - Goodman, Sidney (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 25)
    - Gorbaty, Norman (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 26)
    - Gorelick, Shirley (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 27)
    - Gorey, Edward (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 28)
    - Grado, Angelo John (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 29)
    - Graham, Robert (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 30)
    - Grandee, Joe (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 31)
    - Grashow, James (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 32-33)
    - Gratz, Joan C. (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 34)
    - Green, Norman (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 35)
    - Green, Peter (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 36)
    - Greene, David (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 37)
    - Greene, Herb (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 38)
    - Greene, Matt (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 39-40)
    - Greenfield-Sanders (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 41)
    - Gregory, Jack (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 42-43)
    - Groedel, Burt (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 44)
    - Grooms, Red (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 45)
    - Gropper, William (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 46)
    - Groskinsky, Henry (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 47)
    - Gross, Michael (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 48)
    - Grossman, Henry (Offsite-box 2564, Folder 49-51)
    - Grossman, Henry [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - Grossman, Robert S. (Offsite-box 856, Folder 1)
    - Groth, John (Offsite-box 856, Folder 2)
    - Group Image Enterprises, Inc. (Offsite-box 856, Folder 3)
    - Greurio, Anthony (Offsite-box 856, Folder 4)
    - Guarnieri, Luciano (Offsite-box 856, Folder 5)
    - Gutman, Ilene (Offsite-box 856, Folder 6)
    - Guymon, Linda Fennimore (Offsite-box 856, Folder 7)
    - Guzzi, George (Offsite-box 856, Folder 8)
    - Langley, Helen de (née Haas) (Offsite-box 856, Folder 9)
    - Hafley, Bruce (Offsite-box 856, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Joan (Offsite-box 856, Folder 11-12)
    - Haller, Emmanuel (Offsite-box 856, Folder 13)
    - Halsman, Phillipe (Offsite-box 856, Folder 14)
    - Halstead, Dirck (Offsite-box 856, Folder 15)
    - Hamilton, William (Offsite-box 856, Folder 16)
    - Hampton, Blake (Offsite-box 856, Folder 17-18)
    - Hane, Roger (Offsite-box 856, Folder 19)
    - Hanson, Duane (Offsite-box 856, Folder 20)
    - Harbutt, Paul (Offsite-box 856, Folder 21)
    - Hari, Kenneth (Offsite-box 856, Folder 22)
    - Harris, C. Morgan (Offsite-box 856, Folder 23)
    - Harris, Eleanor (Offsite-box 856, Folder 24)
    - Harrison, Norman (Offsite-box 856, Folder 25)
    - Harvard Cover (Offsite-box 856, Folder 26)
    - Harvey, Robert (Offsite-box 856, Folder 27)
    - Hayes, Marvin (Offsite-box 856, Folder 28)
    - Haydock, Robert (Offsite-box 856, Folder 29)
    - Hedda (Offsite-box 856, Folder 30)
    - Heindel, Robert (Offsite-box 856, Folder 31)
    - Helnwein, Gottfried (Offsite-box 856, Folder 32)
    - Henderson, Alan (Offsite-box 856, Folder 33)
    - Hendricks, James Powell (Offsite-box 856, Folder 34)
    - Hernmarck, Helena Barynina (Offsite-box 856, Folder 35)
    - Hess, Richard (Offsite-box 856, Folder 36-37)
    - Heujil (Offsite-box 856, Folder 38)
    - Hibel, Edna (Offsite-box 856, Folder 39)
    - Hibino, Katsuhiko (Offsite-box 856, Folder 40)
    - Hicks, Philip (Offsite-box 856, Folder 41)
    - Hill, Draper (Offsite-box 856, Folder 42)
    - Hill, James (Offsite-box 856, Folder 43)
    - Hills, Charles (Offsite-box 856, Folder 44)
    - Hinge, Mike (Offsite-box 856, Folder 45)
    - Hinrichs, Kit (Offsite-box 856, Folder 46)
    - Hiro (Offsite-box 856, Folder 47)
    - Hiroshima Cover (Offsite-box 856, Folder 48)
    - Hirsche, H. Lee (Offsite-box 856, Folder 49)
    - Hirschfeld, Al (Offsite-box 856, Folder 50)
    - Hoban, Russell (Offsite-box 856, Folder 51)
    - Hockney, David (Offsite-box 856, Folder 52)
    - Hoff, Margo (Offsite-box 856, Folder 53)
    - Hogarth, Paul (Offsite-box 856, Folder 54)
    - Holland, Brad (Offsite-box 856, Folder 55)
    - Hollingsworth, Al (Offsite-box 856, Folder 56)
    - Hollywood: Smithsonian Institution (Offsite-box 856, Folder 57)
    - Holmes, Nigel (Offsite-box 856, Folder 58)
    - Holton, Gene (Offsite-box 856, Folder 59)
    - Holzman, David (Offsite-box 856, Folder 60)
    - Hoowij, Jan (Offsite-box 856, Folder 61)
    - Horn, Hope (Offsite-box 856, Folder 62)
    - Horowitz, Irwin (Offsite-box 856, Folder 63)
    - Horowitz, Michelle (Offsite-box 856, Folder 64)
    - Hostetler, David (Offsite-box 856, Folder 65)
    - Howard, Len R. (Offsite-box 856, Folder 66)
    - Hudon, Normand (Offsite-box 856, Folder 67)
    - Huehnergarth, John (Offsite-box 856, Folder 68-69)
    - Huffaker, Sandy (Offsite-box 856, Folder 70)